10 terrible Amazon products I bought
this month this is an inflatable sofa
that you fill up just by waving it
through the air then closing the end
creating this comfy bed you can use
anywhere this is a charger that doesn't
need any power you just crank this thing
and you can charge your phone or
anything else in case of an emergency
this is a steel soap bar which actually
cleans your hands without ever running
out and is even backed up by scientific
evidence this is a multi-purpose spatula
thing which lets you flip your eggs or
anything you want to without messing up
or dropping any of your food these are
cologne pumps where you can take out
cologne out of any bottle and store it
in your own separate vial to carry
around this is a sink net so you can
dump food into it when cleaning the
dishes so you don't clog your drain this
is a car mirror extender which lets you
see a much wider view when driving where
you can even see your blind spots this
is a mini vacuum for your desk which
sucks up crumbs and messes and can
pretty much be used anywhere you want
this is a gripper that holds your cables
so they don't fall behind your desk and
can even be used in tons of other ways